I see.
That must have been a
real easy job for you.
It was.
About the job we put on hold.
It's now a go.
You have one week to get it done.
Understood.
You are all good!
Thank you.
My husband, please!
You are really good!
You are good!
I'm good!
We're good!
The same way I love you I'm so
sorry I didn't even talk to you
I honestly hope I had a lot of fun
I am so excited I'm so excited I'm
so excited I'm so excited I'm so
excited I'm so excited I'm so excited
I don't know why you were up now.
So how tough with you can be.
And it is so intense.
Let's dance this at Kauai.
Tell her about Tom like, and
how really Oh come on with that?
Send with police to the pt.
Hey, I fell, I'm back.
meinem Theством.
I've fallen, the bridge to theların.
I bought my own!
Oh I beat the u dos.
I'm not alone.
I wrote Well, I'm not alone, Please
don't myself out of your world.
One miracle pork stew
coming up. Any pig outs?
Hams for the song request.
Here we go in full swine.
The Pure Maid's Killer Kiss.
The Lady Amoe effect is crazy.
We're raking it in like mad.
The curls before swine coffee, oink.
A shot of caffeine into my master.
Great, thank you.
Is something wrong?
No.
Oh,
I just thought it foolish to assume that
pigs wouldn't understand
the value of pearls.
I must say, I don't understand it myself.
I'm sorry.
I think pearls would suit
you nicely, Miss Ronko.
Hmm, it looks like they're hitting it off.
Oh, is that person after Ronko?
I don't see quite the Mitch.
What are you saying?
Come on, piggies!
We have a chance to make
a lot of honey money!
But doesn't Ronko kind of
sort of look interested, too?
Romance between Master and a
maid is strictly off-limits.
Ronko cannot break group rules.
They will disown her.
She wouldn't be able to
get out of Akiba alive.
But I bet you Ronko could
find a way to escape.
No, I mean, it's all over
once a maid falls in love.
Ronko is an Akiba maid.
Akiba maids don't fall in love.
Hey, Ronko.
Was it a riveting conversation?
Do you mean the one I had with Mr.
Seahiro?
Aw, you remember his name.
Yes, I learned it.
What did you talk about?
Well, um, he asked if I wanted to go
out with him somewhere this weekend.
What? All that? For real?
And you said yes to going out with him?
No, I've yet to reply.
Go!
You're meeting him Saturday
at 11 in front of the station.
You just went and told that guy yes?
Come on, girls, he's a banker.
All you have to do is lead him on a
bit and he'll lend us loads of money.
You can't be serious.
Only a banker would carry a briefcase
and wear a trench coat like that.
You know that's not true.
I set things up nicely, so
you go have a word with him.
He's just about to head out. Go on.
But Chief, this sort of
thing isn't allowed, though.
It's just a little date.
Don't worry about it.
All the cafes do it.
It'll be fine.
Thank you, Master.
We await your return.
Are you looking forward to it, Ronko?
What do you mean?
What do I mean?
I mean the date you're going on.
Perhaps I am looking forward to it.
I'm sorry, Ronco.
I should be rooting for your happiness
instead of just being worried.
No.
The idea of finding
happiness is something I
cast aside when I entered
the maid business.
A maid cannot ever hope
for that kind of thing.
But I've definitely had moments of true
happiness getting to be a maid with you.
You're too kind.
If you don't mind, I would love to
help you out with your date, Ronco?
Do you have much experience going
on dates, Nagomi? Of course I do!
Actually, I don't. I lied.
Good morning.
Is something wrong? What's going on?
I apologize.
I must go out today.
Good morning!
Good morning, Nagomi.
How are you?
Take it from me.
A real woman never takes her wallet out.
That's how you become
a woman of high value.
It's what I've always done.
Gotta feel good about how you
look on a date, right girl?
It is the first time you've
been out with a master, right?
Where's this?
It's a dress I got from my babushka.
Wow, you look mad nice.
So, so pretty.
I thought you weren't that
bad looking to begin with.
And the other maids won't recognize
that lovely face of yours.
Listen to me, Ronko.
I think maids deserve to
find true happiness too.
Thank you very much, Nagomi.
Go and enjoy yourself today.
I am determined to appreciate
the time with my master.
Please, excuse me.
Go ahead of me, please.
So, what do you think
happiness is supposed to be?
Have you been waiting long?
No, I haven't. Shall we then?
You look very nice today.
Into the baggy bag.
We'll throw an extra.
Hey, missus, how about you
buy us some fish for dinner?
How nice did you make this
bento I'm afraid that I did
The way that you just talked it's surprising
to hear you now for the first time I
apologize I only know how to speak stiffly
No I really like the way that you talk
Thank you.
The End Broken that might be
it we should buy a kotatsu
we could take it to my
place and make some hot pot.
That would be so warm
i'm afraid we might fall
asleep together but that
would be the best part.
Of it that does sound
rather nice sorry didn't
i just say something
inappropriate you're fine.
There's something wrong
with me when i'm with you
i accidentally let my
guard down for some reason.
Ronko.
Can we walk around for a little longer?
I was actually supposed to do a job today.
I've been fixated on work for so long
that I never take care of myself at all.
I thought that's what I'm supposed to do.
But now, I've finally met you, Ronko.
You've finally met me?
I was worn out emotionally, and
you gave me a place of solace.
As long as I went to Oinkie Doink Cafe,
I could forget about work, and the way
you talked to me would cheer me up.
With your frank but sincere attitude,
you had occupied a place in my
heart before I even knew it.
And because of that, I'm going to
be upfront and honest about this.
Miss Runco, would you run away
with me from Akiba, together?
I'm heading up north on
the night train tomorrow.
You have to make a decision
by the time I leave.
I understand that this proposition
is a bit sudden for you.
I have to...
Tomorrow night at nine, I'll be waiting
at the station's electric town exit.
Is there something that you want from me?
Let me tell you the
story of a certain maid.
Once, there was a young girl who came
to Akiba with dreams of becoming a maid.
Although she got to be a maid, all
she was given was menial tasks.
But then, a master appeared
who took a liking to her.
As her days as a maid had finally begun.
She was tasked to do an important job.
She was to perform a hit.
On the head of a rival maid cafe.
Exactly as some leaked
information had suggested.
The Target's cafe was incredibly
understaffed that day.
That's when
She pulled the trigger.
Chief, no!
In terror,
the maid desperately told herself
she would now rise in the ranks,
and she was happy that she finally
had a master who favored her.
But the truth was harsh.
Him being a master was a lie.
The man had only approached me so he could
eliminate me once I had served my purpose.
Excuse me, are you okay?
Hey, what do you think you're doing?
They never meant to make me a maid.
I was just disposable trash to them.
Must be nice.
I wish I could be a panda.
And that's what led to this.
Do you know of Ronco
Manon from Maid Tea House?
She's the one who got jailed
for avenging her manager, right?
Scary stuff.
That cafe claimed it was anti-violence.
The liars.
Time moved on without me.
Akiba changed over the years.
Hmm?
Hmm.
And when the people of this town
had forgotten what had happened...
Permission to speak
number 96 Ronko Manon 35
years old you appeared
and there I was The one
who murdered the manager
of your cafe the only
reason he approached
you is to kill you Ronko
Someone must have hired
him to do it he may
have given up today but
I can tell it's all a lie
you.
All he cares about is
eliminating his target.
That's why you can't go with him tomorrow.
If you do, he'll kill you
in Hakodate or something.
Bronco, I'm sorry I took the life
of someone who was so dear to you.
I knew I should have told you
sooner, but I just couldn't.
I'm sorry.
I'm such a despicable pit.
Please tell everyone at the cafe
that I enjoyed my time. with them.
Allow me to send you off.
Welcome back!
You were out late.
How did it go?
Did he just kiss you?
You see the panda? Yes, we did.
I got to spend some incredibly
precious time at the zoo.
The arrangements that you made for
me, I very much appreciate them.
That's so great!
That means the cafe's got it made!
I can see those ghosts raining
down on us! Slow your roll! Gross!
Allow me to send you off.
I'm sorry, but I can never forgive you,
Akachi Mashi, for killing Miss Michio.
If that's the case, then why
aren't you going to kill me?
Because I think that Miss Michio
perhaps would never want that of me.
Ronko, why?
Allow me to take care of him. But you...
He's my master, after all.
Could I interest you in our singlet meal?
Oh, wow, thanks! Oiki-doi!
Thank you for letting me bathe first.
Mr.
Suehiro didn't come by
the cafe today, did he?
Yes, that's true.
Seeing you and your
master standing together,
I think you make a really lovely twosome.
To tell you the truth,
I was kind of scared of him when
I first noticed you two together.
But I think that was
only because I was scared
that he would take you
from us and oinky-doink,
Ronco.
You know, we almost drowned, got
killed, we even had to grovel.
I got through all of that
because you were there, Ronko.
If you leave oinky-doink,
I'll definitely be sad.
But please, don't worry about me.
Even when the time finally comes,
I'll start practicing
for your graduation so
you can leave with a
proper smile on your face.
I promise I won't get emotional.
But it looks like you're already crying.
No, that's not what's happening.
I have you to thank, Nagomi.
What?
If it weren't for you,
I never would have considered what
normal happiness might be like.
I'm leaving now.
Ronco?
Listen, Nogomi.
Please take care of
Oinky Doink Cafe for me.
I've decided to settle this my own way.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I seem to have made a mistake.
Hey, hold on.
We're trying to pick her up. No, no.
Was that an accident?
That didn't sound good.
Who are you?
I'm a panda.
That's great, frickin' Panda!
I can't let Ronco live with the
burden of having to kill her master?
Why don't we have a nice little chat?
Is this your idea of making amends?
So you're back to being silent again.
Can I just tell you one thing?
Fifteen years ago,
the one who had me kill Miss Michio was
the current head of Creatureland, Nagi.
She's the one who gave
the order this time, too.
So that's how it's going to be.
There's a lot of people around the world.
That's my life!
I don't know if you're a fool?
I see the blood.
Thank you.
I'm not going to kill Ronco Manon.
I thought I told you that crushing Oinky
Doink Cafe is what the group decided.
Refusing to kill her means defying
the entire Creatureland group.
Interpret it as you wish.
This is my mess.
I've decided to settle it my own way.
You'll cast your life before swine?
You have questionable taste.
I don't need you to
understand Miss Ronko's value.